I want to take the secret of love power,
Gather it up, and send it to you right away
You know I'm the only one for you
I'll be the one by your side in the end
For a while now, I've been wondering if something's wrong
The gloominess on your face really makes me worry
The sky shines a bright blue, and the sun is laughing too
A gentle light pours down on me in seven different colors
The magic cast on my right hand, hey, is the first present I ever got
I'll cherish it, forever, along with these endless feelings of joy
I want to take the secret of love power,
Gather it up, and send it to you right away
You know I'm the only one for you
I'll be the one by your side in the end