Dampening these frozen cheeks as it falls,
Through the power of delusion, amid the depths of despair,
The servants take hold of the blue sky
Rain pours endlessly like exquisite blood
These prayers of madness, these prophecies of sin;
An apocalypse unfurled, the cage the bird is trapped in
Ever the merciless mother, God looks down upon the world
The lambs expose all this falsehood
A domesticated labyrinth of sacrificial livestock
Deep within Her bosom, there exists the serenity unto death
No longer dolls, they shatter the rusted locks of the rotted fencing
Doubt then sprouts from the murmurs of the unknown:
“Though they pull the strings, I mustn't let it end with my deception...”
O sin, become the wings upon their back in the midst of collapsed ruin
As they seek the exit to this dream, this light shines even through despair
Now kill the world, to those who rebel against it
Such is the slaughter brought on by innocence
All is but a phantasm; not a thing is for certain
Forsaken are the hearts soon to be abandoned
Meaningfully a betrayal, an uprising of the soul
There is only the pain—one which becomes the sword tight in their grasp
A storied myth of wicked hearts; in its pages, the knight's awakening unfolds
This present moment becomes the severance of the infinite chain
From darkness without bounds, the hour of awakening has arrived
The Gate unseals our memories as the kneeling ground wavers
The bell rings out perdition, knowing not where to find true salvation
Now kill the world, to those who have awakened in it
Such is the slaughter brought on by innocence
Merely biding their time, for long had they known this
Now begins their inevitable struggle
O sin, become the wings upon their back in the midst of collapsed ruin
As they seek the exit to this dream, this light shines even through despair
The bell rings out perdition, knowing not where to find true salvation
Sin reflects all this falsehood, shattering the mirror of the sky
Now kill the world, to those who are imprisoned by it
Such is the slaughter brought on by innocence