Trust in me
I search for your eyes, which look like the blue sky
Night falls on the street corner I've gazed at for so long
The smile I showed you was the whisper of an innocent dream
The isolation we've wandered into... I want to hide away in it forever
Anyone can wish from the heart, but if you seek that wish out,
Then you can overcome any odds
So don't look back
Let's keep moving forward, without worrying about losing each other
Everything begins with trust
(Begins)
(With trust)
On their own, no one could hope to see what lies beyond the blue sky:
A light guiding our way
All I can do, I will give to you
Because I want to touch—to surrender my heart to someone
(I want to touch)
(To someone)
The two of us will grow even closer, drawing tomorrow in our hearts
Trust in me, because I'm right here
Trust in me