An afterimage flickers
Revealing a warped reality
A world where the boundary of truth and delusions... has simply disappeared
I refuse to fight, so I'll feign ignorance
I reject the world, so I'll stay alone
Grasping it in the ephemeral moment, that castle of sand came crashing down
And in my shaken world, I found an unwavering will
A will that'll chase away tomorrow's clouds
If my one wish could come true,
Then I'd send it in the sky above
As feelings rending the darkness
Sickly dreaming of bloodshed,
I bury what I can of my distorted mentality
A world where the value in making excuses and looking back... has simply disappeared
I refuse to lose, even when fearful
I reject the lies, and I won't lose strength
Grasping at red petals, visions, as they scatter
And in my shaken future, I won't abandon that determination
A will that relinquishes no hope
I'll grant your every wish,
And they'll reach the sky above,
As prayers exceeding light
And in my shaken world, I found an unwavering will
A will that'll chase away tomorrow's clouds
If my one wish could come true,
Then I'd send it in the sky above
As feelings rending the darkness