If you extinguish the light, darkness covers it all:
This miraculous, mysterious space of zeros
The ability to fly in the sky;
Such a specification is negated by another theory
This heart-wrenching scenery warps into a smile
One which beckons “Whose eyes are those eyes?”
Confined between dimensions, unknown to ethics and morals
The fuzzy boundary line is engulfed by chaos...
Ah, mischievous delusions shake my heart
This sky I look up to isn't even blue
Ah, the now-hollow dominion sticks its tongue out in laughter
And reveals itself as a repeating metastasis, eroding all
When confronted to the shriek-inducing craze,
I ran away...