My eyes reflecting a side effect, I continue to trace its outline
I've no words to scream, nothing left I can pray to
The light binds together an image of a mysterious architecture,
A composition akin to betrayal
I averted my gaze, I feigned ignorance
Now the "gaze" delves deep into my consciousness,
And a scant theory disrupts the rhythm of my heart
This casual atmosphere, this impossible distance...
Thus dominance spreads, initiating its infection
Once more...
I become chaos, bearing the endless pain
A place nobody can see, a narcotic area of escapism
Between those buildings, out in that stretch of sky,
Just what dream will be drawn? Ah... There's no answer
I fall into the new world, and unexpectedly...
Static repeats itself in a spiral
Within that flickering light,
You'll find the blue