I know about the bounds of the universe
Out there lies a dead end made of glass
And the visible scenery beyond the glass...
Is the same as what I see when I close my eyes
When the rhythm of your beating heart lapses into disorder,
Your timid voice fails to flee, simply returning to this place once again
Should every living being be ensnared by slothful superfluities,
Would it be best to erase my own existence as well?
If our biorhythms are truly a special thing,
Then both these false memories and treacherous dreams are logically connected
Hey, even if your smile I sometimes see crumbles like papier-mâché,
Painlessly, time goes on
(Everything)
Whose eyes are those eyes?
(Logical)
The play has begun